So we have to drop down so that the form doesn't get too big.
Correct. But actually these things have to be affected.
And now what happens to me, I applied for a credit card.
So I get rejected.
When my decent salary, best score...
You get rejected.
Yes, I get rejected.
I don't even get the Scapia, HDFC card.
Because they are looking at my education.
Okay.
And I don't know what happens to me.
But now I have to apply so much.
Oh my god!
I get card to card, but I don't get such a card.
Because this existing EMI is a big thing.
And this is also one thing.
Debt to debt utilization ratio.
That's what it's called.
Fixed obligation to something.
Yes, correct.
Correct.
That's why your EMI is not fixed.
That means if I get a surprise later, I will lose my trust from the website.
But you will lose your trust.
Yes, but I have to think about something.
Bro, nothing.
This is all mandatory.
But I have to do everything.
Already.
This is it.
Yesterday, I didn't want to give ideas to any applicant.
Because...
I don't want to give ideas to any other applicant.
Oh my god!
Because it increases the loan amount.
Brother, please give me the fixers.
1, 2, 2, 1, 1, 1.
What do you want?
Brother, I want to know who is going to pay the rent.
Whoever is going to pay the rent.
That's why I didn't come.
That's it.